{
    "id": "3c7e483a220147908501c8db5623478c",
    "title": "Will or going to: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "093be4bfa23b44fb99bd7a15e2bde0dd",
            "title": "Will Or Going To",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I can’t lift this box. OK. I ………………… help you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "am going to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I don’t think that she …………………… recognize me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "is going to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Careful! You ………………… fall.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "are going to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ………………….. graduate next year.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "is going to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The flight …………………… at 9 pm.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "departs",
                        "will depart"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………. meet your dad tomorrow afternoon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am going to",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is very hard-working. I think he ........................................ be very successful.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "is going to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... you marry me?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Will",
                        "Are you going to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who do you think …………………….. win the championship?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "is going to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ………………… to America next month.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "fly",
                        "will fly",
                        "am flying"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}